softsurroundings.com 2019-12-19

# Soft Surroundings - Customer Care - Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use

## Privacy Policy & Terms of Use

We appreciate the trust you place in Soft Surroundings, and we are committed to respecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. Our privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. SoftSurroundings.com and SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com are owned by Triad Catalog Co., LLC. Every effort has been made to check our information for accuracy. Descriptive or typographical errors are subject to correction.

We always welcome your questions and feedback. For privacy-related issues, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings  
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076  
Fax: 1-314-521-5780  

**Information We Collect**  
We may collect the following information: first and last name, street address, city, telephone number, e-mail address, your browser or device, and, when necessary, credit card information, when you:

  * Place an order from our catalogs or on our website
  * Make a purchase at one of our retail stores
  * Return an item or make an exchange
  * Inquire about our services
  * Request a catalog
  * Receive a gift package
  * Create an account at SoftSurroundings.com or SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com
  * Subscribe to our e-newsletters or e-mail promotions
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion
  * Participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event

We maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database. 

In the event of a sale or merger of Soft Surroundings, our customers' personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.

**Using Information We Collect**   
At Soft Surroundings, we always want to provide you with the best possible shopping experience and fulfill your orders exactly as you've requested. In order to do this, we collect information that allows us to:

  * Process and track your order
  * Provide the services you request
  * Contact you about the status of an order
  * Send you catalogs or promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you
  * Send you e-mail promotions
  * Identify your product and service preferences
  * Customize our communications to you
  * Provide information concerning product recalls or products you have purchased
  * Improve our merchandise selection and customer service

**Information We Share with Others**  
We contract with other companies to provide certain services, including credit card processing and shipping. We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Soft Surroundings.

From time to time, we make our catalog mailing list (names and addresses only) and general shopping activity available to carefully screened companies whose products we believe will be of interest to you.  We do not share email addresses for such purposes. If you prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings   
1100 N Lindbergh Blvd   
St. Louis, MO 63132   
Phone: 1-800-240-7076  
Fax: 1-314-521-5780  

On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.

**Your Choices**  
We offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or other communications from Soft Surroundings, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings

c/o Customer Service

2280 Schuetz Rd.

Ste. 100

Maryland Heights, MO 63146

If you no longer wish to receive our e-newsletters and e-mail promotions you may electronically [unsubscribe here](https://www.softsurroundings.com/manageemailpreferences/) or contact us at the address above.

If you do not want to receive mailings from other carefully screened companies, please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings

c/o Customer Service

2280 Schuetz Rd.

Ste. 100

Maryland Heights, MO 63146

Please be sure to provide us your exact name and address, or the mailing label from your catalog, so that we can be sure to identify you correctly. Because we plan our mailings in advance, it may take several weeks for your request to become effective. If you continue to receive our communications, please contact us again and we will make every effort to correct the situation.

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**  
A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our website. 

If you set your browser to refuse cookies, please call us at 1-800-240-7076 to place your order.

We also use cookies and pixel tags to tell us what parts of our website you have visited. Pixel tags also enable us to send you e-mail in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an e-mail message from us.

We may use third party companies to provide advertising services and/or to collect certain information when you visit and interact with our website. These third-party companies may collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this website [and/or other websites] in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These third-party companies may use cookies and other technologies to recognize your browser to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. You may visit the Network Advertising Initiative, www.networkadvertising.org/choices or the Digital Advertising Alliance, http://www.aboutads.info/, to learn more about interest-based advertising, or to opt out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests on your browser, from their respective members and participants.

We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Soft Surroundings.

We also engage a third-party partner for the purpose of identifying users and delivering to them marketing on our behalf (i.e. email or direct mail). Our partners may collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, and information about your browser or operating system; may combine personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources; and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. This activity enables them to identify you to facilitate the delivery of marketing on our behalf. To opt out of recognition services, please go [here](https://idx.listrakbi.com/opt-out.html). To opt out of third-party cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.com.info/choices.

We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with relevant online display advertising tailored to your interests.  To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, click [here.](http://dtmc.softsurroundings.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2322&cname=Soft%20Surroundings&cmagic=228bbc&clogo=2322.png&loc=us&lang=en-us)

 **California Privacy Rights**  
Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, Soft Surroundings customers living in the State of California can request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. For requests, please contact Soft Surroundings via the contact information below.

**How We Use E-mail**   
When you provide us your e-mail address, we will send you e-mails necessary to process your order or respond to a request. For example, after you place an order at SoftSurroundings.com and SoftSurroundingsOutlet.com, you will receive an e-mail confirmation and, in most cases, an e-mail with delivery tracking information.  We may also use information about you to communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, including marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.

To provide you with a more seamless customer experience, we keep records of your transactions, both online and in-store. For example, if you use a credit or debit card or give the sales associate your email address when you make a purchase in our store, we may associate that information with your online customer account. We may use information about your purchases to email you about other products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

**Links to Other Sites**   
Occasionally we provide links on our website to other sites we think you will enjoy. These sites operate independently of Soft Surroundings and have established their own privacy and security policies. For the best online experience, we strongly encourage you to review the policies at any site you visit.

**Updating or Reviewing Your Information**  
To update your customer information (name, address, telephone number and e-mail address), please contact us at:

Soft Surroundings

c/o Customer Service

2280 Schuetz Rd.

Ste. 100

Maryland Heights, MO 63146  
info@softsurroundings.com

A limited amount of purchase information also may be available to you. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information.

**Security**  
It is our intent to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you. We use a variety of current technologies and processes for protection of our customer data. We limit the information we provide to outside companies with whom we contract to only what they need to carry out their responsibilities.

When you make a purchase, request a catalog or create an account on our website, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format. See [Secure Online Shopping](https://www.softsurroundings.com/faq/ordering/secure-online-shopping/) for details.

**Privacy of Children on Our Website**  
Our website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**Policy Changes**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change, we will post these changes on our website. We encourage you to review our privacy policy periodically.

**Questions or Comments?**  
For questions, comments or assistance, we invite you to contact us at:

Soft Surroundings

c/o Customer Service

2280 Schuetz Rd.

Ste. 100

Maryland Heights, MO 63146

Phone: 1-800-240-7076  
Fax: 1-314-521-5780
